Felipe Lobo La Yunta

Brazil & Canada

Cell number Canada: (587) 257-5588 Email: layuntaWeb@gmail.com
Cell number Brazil: (62) 98136-4323 Website: portifolio-app-nu.vercel.app/

Education

Computer Science 2020 - 2021

Technological Federal University of Parana – Brazil

Computer Information Technology

Lethbridge College – Lethbridge, AB, Canada

Personal Profile

I am a passionate Web Developer, with about 3 years of programming in different languages, seeking an opportunity to be a junior web developer. I'm a very practical person, open-minded, great at communication. I am ready to help in any way possible with the technologies I already know and with those that I don't know yet and gain a lot of experience.

Work Experience

IOS Developer | Boxes Todo-list

2020 - 2021

2021 - Present

- Mainly worked for me building an App for the Apple Store, called Boxes, it is a Todo-list app;
- Experience in business management;
- Schedules and problem-solving Skills

Web Developer | House Market App

2022 - 2022

- On this project, I worked for myself on building a React app mainly focused on Firebase functionality and design for mobile first.
- Experience with different APIs;
- Experience with Firebase Authentication and Firestore;
- Experience with React Routers;
- GitHub link: https://github.com/layuntaFelipe/house-market-app

Web Developer | "Apple" Support Desk

2022 - 2022

- It was the first project where I worked on the front and back end of a project, working on my database, and on my own API. Having to learn new technologies, but in the end, every new knowledge learned was worth it, because, in the end, I had built a real-world MERN full stack project that worked perfectly;
- Experience with Backend: MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, and Redux;
- Experience building my own API;
- Experience with BCrypt, JsonWebToken APIs, Axios;
- GitHub link: https://github.com/layuntaFelipe/support-desk

- ChefsEye is the main project I'm working on right now, and one of the most complex apps
 I'm building. With a complete backend, with complex database relations, and a responsive, simple, and clean frontend;
- Experience with Backend: MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, and Redux;
- Experience building my own API;
- Experience with BCrypt, JsonWebToken APIs, QRCode, Nodemon, Axios;
- GitHub link: https://github.com/layuntaFelipe/ChefsEye-Software

Professional Skills

- FrontEnd: HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Backend: NodeJS, MongoDB, Firebase, SQL, Express, Redux
- IOS: Swift, SwiftUI

Soft Skills

- Experience in managing a team
- Great Communications Skills
- Quick Learner
- Teamwork
- Speak English, Portuguese, Spanish
- Excellent Problem-Solving Skills

Hobbies

- Karting
- Formula 1
- Read about Business
- CrossFit
- Mountain Bike